A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Organizational and Employment History, Accession 2018:041 FA743
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Organization Charts, 1990-2006; 1; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  - Organization Charts - Fiscal Year 1999 (3 folders), 1998 November-1999 December (Box 2, Folder 16-18)
    Folder 18:) -- Office of the President; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Human Development and Reproductive Health; Office of Vice President -- Education, Media, Arts, and Culture; Education, Knowledge, and Religion; Media, Arts and Culture; Office of the Vice President Peace and Social Justice; Governance and Civil Society Program; Human Rights and International Cooperation Program; Office of Organizational Services; Office of Management Services; Grants Administration and Operations; Grants Administration - EMAC; Grants Administration - PSJ; Grants Administration - Assets; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; The Philippines; China; Vietnam; Russia and Eastern Europe; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Financial and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grants Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services; Facilities Management; Management Information Systems; Information Services; Archives; Records Services; Library; General Services; Information and Records Units; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Fixed Income Investments; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration
    Folder 18:) -- Program Division; Information Technology
  - Organization Charts - Fiscal Year 2000 (3 folders), 1999 November-2000 May (Box 2, Folder 19-21)
    Folder 19:) -- Office of the President; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President -- Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Human Development and Reproductive Health; Office of Organizational Services; Office of the Vice President -- Education, Media, Arts, and Culture; Education, Knowledge, and Religion; Media, Arts, and Culture; Office of Management Services; Grants Administration and Operations; Grants Administration -- EMAC; Grants Administration -- PSJ; Grants Administration --Assets; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; The Philippines; China; Vietnam; Russia and Eastern Europe; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Office of the Vice President -- Peace and Social Justice; Governance and Civil Society Program; Human Rights and International Cooperation Program; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Finance and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grants Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services; Facilities Management; Information Technology; Information Services; Archives; Records Services; Library; General Services; Information and Records Units; Purchasing; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Fixed Income Investments; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration
    Folder 20:) -- Office of the President; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President -- Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Human Development and Reproductive Health; Office of Organizational Services; Office of the Vice President -- Education, Media, Arts, and Culture; Education, Knowledge, and Religion; Media, Arts, and Culture; Office of Management Services; Grants Administration and Operations; Grants Administration -- EMAC; Grants Administration -- PSJ; Grants Administration -- Assets; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; The Philippines; China; Vietnam; Russia and Eastern Europe; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Office of the Vice President -- Peace and Social Justice; Governance and Civil Society Program; Human Rights and International Cooperation Program; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Finance and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grants Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services; Facilities Management; Information Technology; Information Services; Archives; Records Services; Library; General Services; Information and Records Units; Purchasing; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Fixed Income Investments; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration
    Folder 21:) -- Office of the President; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President -- Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Human Development and Reproductive Health; Office of Organizational Services; Office of the Vice President -- Education, Media, Arts, and Culture; Education, Knowledge, and Religion; Media, Arts, and Culture; Office of Management Services; Grants Administration and Operations; Grants Administration -- EMAC; Grants Administration -- PSJ; Grants Administration --Assets; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; The Philippines; China; Vietnam; Russia and Eastern Europe; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Office of the Vice President -- Peace and Social Justice; Governance and Civil Society Program; Human Rights and International Cooperation Program; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Finance and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grants Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services; Facilities Management; Information Technology; Information Services; Archives; Records Services; Library; General Services; Information and Records Units; Purchasing; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Fixed Income Investments; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration
  - Organization Charts - Fiscal Year 2001 (2 folders), 2000 November (Box 3, Folder 22-23)
    Folder 22:) -- Office of the President; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President -- Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Human Development and Reproductive Health; Office of Organizational Services; Office of the Vice President -- Education, Media, Arts, and Culture; Education, Knowledge, and Religion; Media, Arts, and Culture; International Fellowship Program; Office of Management Services; Grants Administration and Operations; Grants Administration -- EMAC; Grants Administration -- PSJ; Grants Administration --Assets; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; The Philippines; China; Vietnam; Russia and Eastern Europe; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Office of the Vice President -- Peace and Social Justice; Governance and Civil Society Program; Human Rights and International Cooperation Program; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Finance and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grants Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services; Facilities Management; Information Technology; Global Infrastructure Services; Information Services; Archives; Records Services; Library; General Services; Information and Records Units; Purchasing; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Fixed Income Investments; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration
    Folder 23:) -- Office of the President; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President -- Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Human Development and Reproductive Health; Office of Organizational Services; Office of the Vice President -- Education, Media, Arts, and Culture; Education, Knowledge, and Religion; Media, Arts, and Culture; International Fellowship Program; Office of Management Services; Grants Administration and Operations; Grants Administration -- EMAC; Grants Administration -- PSJ; Grants Administration -- Assets; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; The Philippines; China; Vietnam; Russia and Eastern Europe; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Office of the Vice President -- Peace and Social Justice; Governance and Civil Society Program; Human Rights and International Cooperation Program; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Finance and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grants Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services; Facilities Management; Information Technology; Global Infrastructure Services; Information Services; Archives; Records Services; Library; General Services; Information and Records Units; Purchasing; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Fixed Income Investments; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration; Office of Human Resources
  - Organization Charts - Fiscal Year 2002 (2 folders), 2001 October-2002 April (Box 3, Folder 24-25)
    Folder 24:) -- Office of the President; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President -- Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Human Development and Reproductive Health; Office of Organizational Services; Office of the Vice President -- Education, Media, Arts, and Culture; Education, Knowledge, and Religion; Media, Arts, and Culture; International Fellowship Funds; Office of Management Services; Grants Administration and Operations; Budgets and International Operations/Grant Information; Grants Administration -- EMAC; Grants Administration -- PSJ; Grants Administration -- Assets; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; The Philippines; China; Vietnam; Russia and Eastern Europe; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Office of the Vice President -- Peace and Social Justice; Governance and Civil Society Program; Human Rights and International Cooperation Program; Special Initiative on Africa; Project on Strategic Philanthropy; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Financial and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grants Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services - Office of the Director; Facilities Management; Information Technology; Global Infrastructure Services; Program Systems Development; Management Systems Development; Ford Foundation New York Infrastructure Services; Information Services; Archives; Records Services; Library; Database Services; Information and Records Units; Purchasing; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Fixed Income Investments; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration; Information Services; Archives; Records Services; Library; Database Services; Information and Records Units
    Folder 25:) -- Office of the President; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President -- Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Human Development and Reproductive Health; Office of Organizational Services; Office of the Vice President -- Education, Media, Arts, and Culture; Education, Knowledge, and Religion; Media, Arts, and Culture; International Fellowship Funds; Office of Management Services; Grants Administration; Grants Administration -- EMAC; Grants Administration -- PSJ; Grants Administration -- Assets; Budgets and International Operations/Grant Information; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; The Philippines; China; Vietnam; Russia and Eastern Europe; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Peace and Social Justice; Governance and Civil Society Program; Human Rights and International Cooperation Program; Special Initiative on Africa; Project on Strategic Philanthropy; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Financial and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grant Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services - Office of the Director; Facilities Management; Information Technology; Global Infrastructure Services; Program Systems Development; Management Systems Development; Ford Foundation New York Infrastructure Services; Information Services; Research Services; Resource Management; Library; Technical Services; Purchasing; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Fixed Income Investments; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration
  - Organization Charts - Fiscal Year 2003 (2 folders), 2002 November-2003 May (Box 3, Folder 26-27)
    Folder 26:) -- Information Technology; Office of the President; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President -- Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Office of Management Services; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; The Philippines; China; Vietnam; Russia and Eastern Europe; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Office of the Vice President -- Knowledge, Creativity and Freedom; Education, Sexuality, and Religion; Media, Arts, and Culture; Peace and Social Justice Program; Governance and Civil Society Program; Human Rights; Special Initiative on Africa; Grant Craft Program; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Financial and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grants Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services - Office of the Director; Facilities Management; Information Technology; Global Infrastructure Services; Program Systems Development; Management Systems Development; Ford Foundation New York Infrastructure Services; Information Services; Research Services; Information Processing Services; Collection Development Services; Technical Services; Purchasing; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Fixed Income Investments; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration
    Folder 27:) -- Office of the President; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President -- Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Office of Management Services; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; The Philippines; China; Vietnam; Russia and Eastern Europe; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Office of the Vice President -- Knowledge, Creativity and Freedom; Education, Sexuality, and Religion; Media, Arts, and Culture; Peace and Social Justice Program; Governance and Civil Society Program; Human Rights; Special Initiative on Africa; Grant Craft Program; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Financial and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grants Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services - Office of the Director; Facilities Management; Information Technology; Global Infrastructure Services; Program Systems Development; Management Systems Development; Ford Foundation New York Infrastructure Services; Information Services; Research Services; Information Processing Services; Collection Development Services; Technical Services; Purchasing; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Investment Administration; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration; General Management
  - Organization Charts - Fiscal Year 2004 (2 folders), 2003 October-2004 May (Box 3, Folder 28-29)
    Folder 28:) -- Office of the President; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President -- Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Office of Management Services; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; China; Vietnam; Russia and Eastern Europe; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Office of the Vice President -- Knowledge, Creativity and Freedom; Education, Sexuality, and Religion; Media, Arts, and Culture; Peace and Social Justice Program; Governance and Civil Society Program; Human Rights; Special Initiative on Africa; Grant Craft Program; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Financial and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grants Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services - Office of the Director; Facilities Management; Information Technology; Global Infrastructure Services; Program Systems Development; Management Systems Development; Ford Foundation New York Infrastructure Services; Information Services; Research Services; E-Content and Technical Services; Purchasing; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Investment Administration; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration
    Folder 29:) -- Organization; Office of the President; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President -- Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Office of Management Services; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; China; Vietnam; Russia and Eastern Europe; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Office of the Vice President -- Knowledge, Creativity and Freedom; Education, Sexuality, and Religion; Media, Arts, and Culture; Peace and Social Justice Program; Governance and Civil Society Program; Human Rights; Special Initiative on Africa; Grant Craft Program; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Financial and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grants Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services - Office of the Director; Facilities Management; Information Technology; Global Infrastructure Services; Program Systems Development; Management Systems Development; Ford Foundation New York Infrastructure Services; Information Services; Research Services; Information Processing Services; E-Content and Technical Services; Purchasing; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Investment Administration; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration
  - Organization Charts - Fiscal Year 2005 (2 folders), 2004 November-2005 May (Box 3, Folder 30-31)
    Folder 30:) -- Organization; Office of the President; General Management; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President -- Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Office of Management Services; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; China; Vietnam; Russia and Eastern Europe; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Office of the Vice President -- Knowledge, Creativity and Freedom; Education, Sexuality, and Religion; Media, Arts, and Culture; Peace and Social Justice Program; Governance and Civil Society Program; Human Rights; Special Initiative on Africa; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Financial and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grants Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services - Office of the Director; Facilities Management; Information Technology; Global Infrastructure Services; Program Systems Development; Management Systems Development; Ford Foundation New York Infrastructure Services; Information Services; Research Services; Information Processing Services; E-Content and Technical Services; Purchasing; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Fixed Income Investments; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration
    Folder 31:) -- Organization; General Management; Office of the President; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President -- Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Office of Management Services; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; China; Vietnam; Russia; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Office of the Vice President -- Knowledge, Creativity and Freedom; Education, Sexuality, and Religion; Media, Arts, and Culture; Peace and Social Justice Program; Governance and Civil Society Program; Human Rights; Special Initiative on Africa; Grant Craft Program; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Financial and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grants Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services - Office of the Director; Facilities Management; Information Technology; Global Infrastructure Services; Program Systems Development; Management Systems Development; Ford Foundation New York Infrastructure Services; Information Services; Research Services; Information Processing Services; E-Content and Technical Services; Purchasing; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Fixed Income Investments; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration